John Edward S. Campita

155 Wellesley Street E, Toronto, ON M4Y1J4 mobile: 647.917.3488 email: johncampita@gmail.com

Professional Summary

A creative professional with 10 years of experience, skilled in concept development and relationship building. Has experience in overseeing creative projects from conceptualization to development, and implementation. Highly knowledgeable in the areas of graphic design and social media marketing.

Work Experience:

Troopr Creative (January 2017 - Present)

Art Director

- Served as Art Director for a start-up agency.
- Acquired several clients from the F&B industries such as:
 - Ramen Nagi (Branding & Social Media)
 - o Tendon Akimitsu (Branding & Social Media)
 - o Fat Fook Taiwanese Restaurant (Branding & Social Media)
 - Kettle Restaurant (Branding)
 - o Rackshack (Social Media)
 - o Wolfgang's Steakhouse (Social Media)
 - o Florabel Group of Restaurants (Social Media)
 - Racks Philippines (Social Media)
 - Tenya Philippines (Branding & Social Media)
 - Café Mediterranean (Social Media)
- Responsible for improving branding, design & communication materials while adhering to the client's brand identity.
- Created 360 social media content and maximized my skillset in art direction, graphic design, photography, and copywriting.

Okada Manila (Sep 2016 - January 2017)

Design Content Manager

- Spearheaded digital campaigns for Okada Manila's grand opening.
- Stronger social media performance versus its direct competitors i.e Resorts World, Solaire, COD.
- Facebook community grew 3x in less than 4 months (118,927 fans as of 12/29/16).
- Produces digital video campaigns with third party suppliers.
- Multimedia artist for ad hoc content & moment marketing.

Gobo Creative (May 2016 - Sep 2016)

Art Director

- Ideation and brand development for new accounts.
- Develop print & digital materials for clients such as:
 - o Watsons Philippines
 - Kojie-San
 - o SM Beauty
- Generate creative ideas during strategic and conceptual brainstorming.
- · Landed Scent Therapy account and developed their brand identity such as company logo and product packaging.

Expressions Stationery Shop Inc. (Jun 2015 - May 2016)

Creatives Manager

- Led the complete rebranding of all business units such as:
 - Expressions
 - Mart One Department Store
 - o Mi Department Store
 - My Basics
- Managed all aspects of campaign design including ideation, development, and implementation.

The Moment Group of Restaurants (Feb 2013 - May 2015)

Creative Communications Head

- Pioneer team for the branding of the following restaurants:
 - o 8 Cuts Burgers
 - o Manam Comfort Filipino
- · Established and grew brand's presence in social media platforms
- Meticulously follow and implement corporate brand guidelines across a team of creatives.
- Led special projects as needed by the business i.e packaging development, visual merchandising, business acquisition decks, etc.

Education

Diploma in Advertising & Graphic Design

Humber College

2022 - present

Bachelor of Arts in Animation

De La Salle-College of Saint Benilde

2008 - 2011

Educated in Freehand Illustration, Photography, Video, Digital Arts, Flash Animation, Experimental Animation, Interactive gaming, 2D & 3D animation, Sound Design, Scriptwriting, Video Editing, and Web design.

Primary and Secondary Education

Colegio San Agustin Makati

1997 – 2008

Core Competencies

Proficiency in

Art Direction, Graphic Design, Copywriting, Illustrator, Photography, Social Media Marketing, Adobe Creative Cloud, MS Office